<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Announcements on Hostify</title><link>https://blog.hostify.gg/categories/announcements/</link><description>Recent content in Announcements on Hostify</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.hostify.gg/categories/announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing Hostify</title><link>https://blog.hostify.gg/p/welcome/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.hostify.gg/p/welcome/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.hostify.gg/p/welcome/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Introducing Hostify" />&lt;h1 id="introducing-hostify-your-high-performance-budget-friendly-game-server-hosting-solution">Introducing Hostify: Your High Performance Budget-Friendly Game Server Hosting Solution
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>Calling all casual gamers and community leaders! We’re thrilled to announce the launch of &lt;strong>&lt;a class="link" href="https://Hostify.GG" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Hostify&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> — a brand-new platform dedicated to making game server hosting both &lt;strong>powerful&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>budget-friendly&lt;/strong>. If you’ve been searching for a reliable server to host your ARK, Rust, or Palworld worlds (with Minecraft support on the way), you’ve come to the right place.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="how-hostify-stands-out">How Hostify Stands Out
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>While other providers often cram multiple servers on shared hardware, &lt;strong>&lt;a class="link" href="https://Hostify.GG" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Hostify&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> is built on the principle of &lt;strong>dedicated CPU&lt;/strong> — ensuring your server won’t slow down when you and your friends log in for a weekend of gaming. Plus, because we’re an indie platform with lower overhead, we’re able to pass on those savings directly to you, meaning more gaming for less cost.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-personal-journey-in-engineering">A Personal Journey in Engineering
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>My passion for creating &lt;strong>&lt;a class="link" href="https://Hostify.GG" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Hostify&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> comes from years of hands-on experience in a variety of engineering roles. I started off as a &lt;strong>graduate software engineer&lt;/strong> with a curious mind that led me to explore everything from frontend and backend development to security operations and systems engineering. This broad skill set culminated in my ability to &lt;strong>develop an end-to-end platform&lt;/strong> that automates the entire process of maintaining game servers through an easy-to-use Web UI.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In other words, &lt;strong>&lt;a class="link" href="https://Hostify.GG" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Hostify&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> isn’t just another hosting service — it’s the result of countless hours (and late nights!) spent perfecting a seamless and efficient way for you to launch and manage your game servers without the usual headaches.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="why-youll-love-hostify">Why You&amp;rsquo;ll Love Hostify
&lt;/h2>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Straightforward Setup&lt;/strong>: Skip the complex installations. Our automated platform helps you get your server up and running in minutes.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Dedicated Resources&lt;/strong>: Enjoy performance boosts from dedicated CPU and faster hardware — no more overcrowded servers.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Budget-Friendly&lt;/strong>: As an indie developer, I keep overhead costs low, so you can rent server space without breaking the bank.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Ongoing Game Support&lt;/strong>: We currently offer hosting for ARK, Rust, and Palworld, and are excited to roll out Minecraft support soon!&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="ready-to-get-started">Ready to Get Started?
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>We’re &lt;strong>live as of today&lt;/strong> and would love for you to be part of our growing community. Whether you’re a casual gamer wanting a lag-free session with friends or a community leader looking to host large events without emptying your wallet, &lt;strong>&lt;a class="link" href="https://Hostify.GG" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Hostify&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> has you covered.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Head over to &lt;strong>&lt;a class="link" href="https://Hostify.GG" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Hostify.GG&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> and see for yourself why our service is the perfect fit for your next gaming adventure. Sign up now, customize your server, and get your friends together for a truly seamless multiplayer experience!&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>We hope you enjoy exploring &lt;strong>&lt;a class="link" href="https://Hostify.GG" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Hostify&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> as much as we enjoyed creating it. The gaming community deserves top-tier performance at an affordable price, and we’re here to deliver exactly that. See you online!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>